export const easyQuestions = [
  { question: "1 + 3 = ?", selections: [4, 6, 1, 9], correctAnswer: 4 },
  { question: "12 + 29 = ?", selections: [30, 36, 41, 50], correctAnswer: 41 },
  { question: "9 - 4 = ?", selections: [6, 3, 7, 5], correctAnswer: 5 },
  { question: "31 - 12 = ?", selections: [18, 19, 10, 20], correctAnswer: 19 },
  { question: "3 * 4 = ?", selections: [15, 19, 11, 12], correctAnswer: 12 },
  { question: "12 * 6 = ?", selections: [72, 80, 64, 89], correctAnswer: 72 },
  { question: "12 / 6 = ?", selections: [10, 3, 5, 2], correctAnswer: 2 },
  { question: "60 / 6 = ?", selections: [7, 4, 10, 6], correctAnswer: 10 },
  {
    question: "21 + 6 - 9 = ?",
    selections: [18, 20, 22, 16],
    correctAnswer: 18,
  },
  {
    question: "3 * 8 / 2 = ?",
    selections: [14, 12, 10, 18],
    correctAnswer: 12,
  },
];

export const mediumQuestions = [
  {
    question: "8 * (4 - 2) = ?",
    selections: [14, 16, 35, 30],
    correctAnswer: 16,
  },
  {
    question: "15 - 3(2 + 1) = ?",
    selections: [6, 10, 4, 12],
    correctAnswer: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "24 / (6 - 4) = ?",
    selections: [20, 0, 12, 18],
    correctAnswer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "Find the missing terms in multiple of 3: 3, 6, 9, __, 15",
    selections: [10, 14, 12, 11],
    correctAnswer: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "Find the missing terms in division of 4: 36, 32, __, 24, 20",
    selections: [26, 28, 30, 31],
    correctAnswer: 28,
  },
  {
    question: "The product of 121 x 0 x 200 x 25 is",
    selections: [600000, 605000, 61000000, 0],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the next prime number after 5?",
    selections: [7, 11, 13, 10],
    correctAnswer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "How many sides does a pentagon have?",
    selections: [4, 5, 6, 7],
    correctAnswer: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "The sum of angle of a square is?",
    selections: [180, 720, 1080, 360],
    correctAnswer: 360,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the shapes that stated below has same length at all sides?",
    selections: ["Square", "Rectangle", "Parallelograms", "Trapezium"],
    correctAnswer: "Square",
  },
];

export const hardQuestions = [
  {
    question: "x + 3 = 5. x = ?",
    selections: [1, 4, 2, -2],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "x - 3 = 7. x = ?",
    selections: [10, 8, 13, 20],
    correctAnswer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "2x + 13 = 47. x = ?",
    selections: [39, 34, 30, 20],
    correctAnswer: 34,
  },
  {
    question: "0.5x - 12 = 10. x = ?",
    selections: [45, 50, 48, 44],
    correctAnswer: 44,
  },
  {
    question: "0.5x - 12 = 10. x = ?",
    selections: [45, 50, 48, 44],
    correctAnswer: 44,
  },
  {
    question: "2x^2 -8 = 10. x = ?",
    selections: [4, 1, 3, 5],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "3x + 10 = x + 30. x = ?",
    selections: [9, 10, 13, 15],
    correctAnswer: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "3x + 10 = 38 - x. x = ?",
    selections: [9, 5, 12, 7],
    correctAnswer: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "2x + y = 8, y + x = 5. x = ?",
    selections: [3, 5, 2, 6],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "3x - 2y = 10, 2y - x = 2. y = ?",
    selections: [9, 7, 3, 4],
    correctAnswer: 4,
  },
];
